[
  {
    "questionText": "How many months are there in 5 years?",
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Which number Apollo mission was the spaceflight that landed the first two men on the Moon?",
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "How much is in a Bakers Dozen?",
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Which age do you have to reach to be eligible to become President of the United States?",
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Which two numbers make up the international direct-dial phone call code to the United Kingdom?",
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "In music, how many inches in diameter was the old 45 rpm vinyl single?",
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "What do the sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel add up to?",
    "answer": "666"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "How many sides does a tridecagon have?",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "How many zeros are there in 1 quadrillion pound?",
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "The roman numeral XXIV is equivalent to which number?",
    "answer": "24"
  }
]